Invocation by a retired pastor of First Christian Church, Mr. Leon Weiss.
Father, we count on you for all we do and I thank you Lord that this group
recognizes your presence and we ask for your help. We ask you to make us wise, make us kind,
help everyone making decisions to have your special wisdom.
But Father, we trust you and we ask you to help us. In Jesus name I pray. Amen.
For the United States of America, and to the Republic for which it stands, one nation under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
Four, public input unscheduled personal appearances.
Five, discussion on possible action on five A, claims list.
Motion to approve. Second.
Barns. Aye. Jones. Aye. Dunkel. Aye. Parker. Aye.
Five B, claims list for advanced auto group. Motion to approve.
Jones. Aye. Barnes. Aye. Parker. Abstain.
Five C, minutes from the April 7th, 2026 regular meeting.
Make motion to approve. I'll second.
Jones. Aye. Barnes. Aye. East Step. Aye. Dunkel. Aye. Parker.
Aye.
Item six, other new business, if any, which has risen since posting this agenda.
Seven, staff reports.
Eight, trustee community announcements.
Nine, trust manager communications.
Ten, adjournment.
Dunkel. Aye. East Step. Aye. Jones. Aye. Barnes. Aye. Parker. Aye.